tweetfind.com 2012-10-17

# Privacy Twitter Directory and Search Twitter Accounts

| 

**TweetFind.com Internet/Web Privacy Policy**

**  
**  
We have created this statement to communicate our commitment to privacy. We are dedicated to providing a safe, secure and enjoyable environment in which to search a Twitter directory of the best sites online. This statement details our current information gathering procedures, which are subject to change without notice. In order to confirm your understanding of our Privacy Policy, it is suggested that you review this Privacy Policy from time to time. This Privacy 

**Policy covers the following practices:**

* What personally identifiable information Tweetfind collects.  
* How Tweetfind uses the information.  
* What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.  
* What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of    information under Tweetfind control.  
* How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

For any questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy, please use our Contact form.

Information Collection and Use TWeetFind is the sole owner of the information collected on Tweetfind.com We collect information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

**Registration**  
In order to submit a site for review, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information including name, twitter address, web address and email address. We use this information to create their profile/listing at TweetFind.com and at times contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest. 

**PROFILE**  
We store information that we collect through log files, and via the information provided during the Tweetfind Submit service, to create a profile listing of our users. A profile listing is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their information. 

**We DO NOT share your profile with other third parties.**

**LOG FILES**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Communications from the Site**  
SPECIAL OFFERS AND UPDATES  
Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, or special deals. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Opt-out sections in the emails.

**SERVICE ANNOUNCEMENTS**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications - these communications are not promotional in nature.

**CUSTOMER SERVICE**  
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email.

**Sharing**  
**LEGAL DISCLAIMER**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**AGGREGATE INFORMATION (non-personally identifiable)**  
We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This information includes: page views, unique visitors, browsers, and additional broad demographical data. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS**

TweetFind shares Web site usage information about users with reputable third party advertisers for the purpose of targeting our advertisements. Be advised that though we make every effort to accept only reputable advertisers, that we cannot held responsible for the Privacy Policies of any advertiser, promotional link, sponsor, or other third party. Please make sure to check the individual Privacy Policy of any third party site that you visit.

Instances in which Tweetfind Will Share Users' Personal Information:

THIRD PARTY INTERMEDIARIES  
We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for services(PayPal.com), Paypal is a service allows members to send money without sharing financial information, with the flexibility to pay using their account balances, bank accounts, credit cards or promotional financing. With more than 94 million active accounts in 190 markets and 24 currencies around the world, PayPal enables global ecommerce. 

**BUSINESS TRANSITIONS**  
In the event Tweetfind goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.

**CHOICE/OPT-OUT**  
Users who no longer wish to receive promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by selecting the opt-out on the emails. or they could email us at:  info@tweetfind.com.

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Tweetfind, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Security**  
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our financial department or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees are encouraged to use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Our employees are reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users information is protected. 

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can contact us at:  info@tweetfind.com

**Modifying Personal Information**  
If a users personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct or update usersâ€™ personally identifiable information. This can be done sending us an email at: info@tweetfind.com

**  
Notice of Change**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If, however, we are going to use users personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will 

post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.  
Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: **info@tweetfind.com**

|   
---|---|---
